

# **Profile**

Jr. software developer, specialized in modern apps.

Knowledgeable in Front-End, UI and UX and equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. Proficient and certified in an assortment of technologies, including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Type Script, SQL, PHP, currently learning Python.

Bringing forth several years of experience and expertise in leading a team up to 15 people . Accustomed to working well with others and committed to project guidelines.

# **Employment History**

#### Freelancer

JANUARY 2023

At this moment I am developing projects for various clients, from single page web pages to more complex applications such as a car maintenance tracker that includes registration, login and data collection.

## Owner, Baketo, Bogotá

OCTOBER 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2022

# Manager of Engineering area, Moraequipos SAS, Bogotá

MAY 2017 - OCTOBER 2020

## Full time Mother, Bogotá

DECEMBER 2015 - OCTOBER 2017

## Researcher of new lines of business, Moraequipos SAS, Bogotá

 $\mathsf{MARCH}\ \mathtt{2015}\ -\ \mathsf{DECEMBER}\ \mathtt{2015}$ 

#### Improvement process manager, Ilko Peru SAC, Lima

SEPTEMBER 2014 - FEBRUARY 2015

# Education

## Modern Web Developer, W3 Schools

AUGUST 2022 - JANUARY 2023

## Front-End Developer, W3 Schools

AUGUST 2022 - NOVEMBER 2022

## Industrial Engineering, Universidad de Los Andes, Bogotá

AUGUST 2009 - MAY 2014

# Courses

## Negotiation, Universidad de Los Andes

JULY 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2018

## Management control, Universidad de Los Andes

JANUARY 2017 - MARCH 2017

## Project Evaluation and Management, Universidad de Los Andes

JANUARY 2016 - MAY 2016

## **Details**

Bogotá

Colombia

+57 302 201 2043

gaby@bygabymora.com

# Links

LinkedIn

Github

**Twitter** 

WhatsApp

www.bygabymora.com

# **Skills**

HTML5

CSS3

**JavaScript** 

React.js (with Hooks)

Type Script

SQL/MySQL

Bootstrap

Mui Component Library for

React.js

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Leadership Skills

Fast Learner

Ability to Work in a Team

# Languages

English

Spanish; Castilian